jdlighting.com.au 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy | JD Lighting | JD Lighting

This privacy policy sets out how JD Lighting uses and protects any information that you give JD Lighting while using this website. JD Lighting is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

  1. At JD Lighting, we understand our customer’s concerns about their personal information and how it is collected and used. We want to assure you that we are committed to protecting and handling our client’s privacy securely and carefully.
  2. For JD Lighting to process your order, we need information such as your name, email or contact number, delivery address and payment details. We may share this information, and only that information which is absolutely necessary, with those third parties that are involved in the processing of your order. For example, the financial institution that issued your credit card and the shipping carrier that delivers your order. Other information will also be collected with your permission from time to time. This will normally include preferences such as likes or dislikes.
  3. Your Personal Information:
    * This will be collected when you log on, place an order or register with us.
    * This will not be collected when you visit our web site and surf our product list.
    * When you place an order and/or register your details with us, you will be asked for the following personal information: your name, e-mail address, mailing address, delivery address and any special delivery instructions and phone number.
    * The information we collect about our clients is used to process orders and to personalise their shopping experience.
    * Your personal information will not be shared, sold, rented or bartered to any third party without your permission.

### Use of Cookies

JD Lighting collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use – will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. – Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

We use Google AdWords remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

This website uses Microsoft Bing Ad's free tracking features on its webpages. If we are contacted online, the destination page will have code on it that will help us understand the path you took to arrive on that page.

We use Google AdWords remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

We respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

  * To fulfill your requests for services.
  * To protect ourselves from liability.
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law

JD Lighting has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.
